Lady Tamayo!
Good evening, Miss Tamayo.
It's dangerous, you know, leaving your window open at night like this.
I don't blame you, the moon is truly gorgeous tonight.
Nice to meet you.
No need to worry.
I'm one of Kaguya Ubuyashiki's messengers.
Hmph.
I understand you have suspicions.
I don't blame you.
I already assumed before meeting you
that it would be hard to gain your trust the way Tanjiro has.
Oh well.
What does he intend to do?
Ubuyashiki.
Is he trying to deceive me somehow?
And Yushiro?
You have my word that Yushiro is safe.
Listen.
You can hear his footsteps running towards us.
Lady Tamayo!
And now, shall I state my business here?
In the Demon Slayer Corps, there is a young girl who is also well-versed in demon physiology.
We'd like you to collaborate with her and look into the changes to Nezuko.
Help us defeat Muzan Kibutsuji.
The decision is yours.
We'll be waiting at the Ubuyashiki Mansion.
You're summoning me, a demon, to the headquarters of the Demon Slayer Corps?
I'll be waiting for a favorable response from you.
Lady Tamayo!
Yushiro.
Let's clear out of the house now!
I'm ready to go!
It's not like that.
Now that Nezuko has managed to conquer the sun,
something's been set in motion.
No.
It's possible change was set in motion long before that.
What happened on that fateful day
has at last begun to swell
and become one large wave.
If that's the case...
It can't be, Lady Tamayo!
Either way, we will be leaving this house.
However, things are different this time.
I'm going to start compiling the research I've done up till now.
But I will need your help, Yushiro.
Quickly.
This may very well be our last move.
Now let's go to the Demon Slayer Corps headquarters.
The Ubuyashiki Mansion.
Demon Slayer Season.
Was there a return?
Who did he altre?
Not really.
Not yet.
Doesn't take the dollar.
The era.
Not yet.
This must be,
A 해 look.
Mきます,
Died of the Bay.
To be the Fiona.
Oh,
Fakezur ‑‑
M Forsy만!
M peu because He's one,
I onlyξed by a parent.
That should be lonely.
There's a dragon or a son in the system.
For a reason to find out where you might speak
The warning about your will the evil
Don't understand the edge of your life
Oh
Master.
Tanjiro, how are your wounds healing?
I'm ashamed to admit it, but I am no longer capable of moving.
And though I'd like to speak with Giyu myself, it doesn't look like that'll be possible.
As this is a very important time for us, I'd like to strive together as one as we push forward with all our might.
And so, would you mind being the one to talk to Giyu for me?
My hope is that Giyu who burdens himself with negative thoughts can start to look forward again.
So be persistent. Don't give up until he sees the light.
Mr. Giyu...
Yes!
Huh? It's awfully early, Mr. Tanjiro. Where are you heading?
Ms. Aoi.
Are you leaving? For Hashira training?
No, I'm not. But I have to see someone before that.
I guess that should be fine then.
Ms. Aoi?
What is it?
There's something that I'd like to ask you. Is that okay?
Mm.
Let's say that there's someone who feels like they're all alone.
How would you go about convincing that person that they're not alone?
Is there a way to do it while actually getting through to them?
Well, if anyone knows the answer to that, it's not me.
But Mr. Tanjiro, above all else, you want to cheer this person up, don't you?
Well, if it were me, I'd just want to be left alone.
By the way, are you leaving now?
Uh, yes.
Wait here a minute, okay?
Oh.
Are you going to visit just one person?
Yes.
This sure is complicated.
They're very simple, but I've made you some rice balls.
There should be enough for both you and that person.
Whatever you do, you need to eat your fill first.
Or else you'll never become healthy in body and soul.
Miss Aoi…
Thank you!
Bye now!
Excuse me…
Mr. Tomioka?
Hello?
Sorry to bother you.
Mr. Diyu?
It's me!
Are you in there?
It's me, Tanjiro Kamado!
Hello?
Alright, I'm coming in!
Coming in?
No.
He must have said I'm leaving.
I simply misheard.
No!
So long story short, everyone's been busy training.
I know.
Oh, so you knew!
That's great!
Too close.
And I'll be cleared for active duty in seven days.
You think you can train me then?
I can't.
But why not?
I'm catching a faint whiff of anger from you.
But what could have you upset?
I'm upset that you never mastered water breathing to its perfection.
After all, you were meant to become the next water Hashira.
Well, look, I'm very sorry about that.
But I talked to Mr. Urokodaki about it.
Changing the style you started with to develop a new breathing technique apparently isn't all that uncommon.
And since water breathing moves are so in line with the fundamentals, it can spawn a lot of techniques.
That's not what I'm talking about.
We're still missing a water Hashira.
Someone has to assume the mantle, and I suppose I hoped it would be you.
Still missing a water Hashira?
But you're the water Hashira!
I'm not the water Hashira.
Get out.
So be persistent. Don't give up until he sees the light.
Right!
Mr. Giyu!
I brought some rice balls with me.
Would you like to eat them together?
They say you can't be angry.
After a good meal and a full stomach.
Alright, I'll just leave them here for you.
Mr. Giyu!
You're up early.
You must have enjoyed those rice balls.
That's great!
Please wait!
Mr. Giyu!
Where are you headed, Mr. Giyu?
What are you up to?
Are you on patrol?
It does feel like demon sightings have settled down, doesn't it?
No demons here, huh?
Thank goodness!
So we can start training now!
Mr. Giyu!
Do you want to come training?
Training!
Everyone's waiting for you!
Mr. Giyu!
Mr. Giyu?
I see you!
Mr. Giyu!
Oh no…
Is this going to last forever?
Mr. Giyu!
Mr. Giyu…
Mr. Giyu —
Mr. Giyu!
Mr. Giyu—
That's right. I didn't take it alone. There was a boy, whose family had also been killed by demons. His name was Sabito. I'll never forget his peach-colored hair. Or what happened that day.
Sabito and Mr. Kiyu.
I was 13 back then. We were the same age and alone in the world. We became friends quickly.
Sadly, Sabito had a strong sense of justice, and yet a kind and gentle heart.
The only one who died during that year's selection was Sabito.
He managed to kill nearly every demon on that mountain single-handedly.
In the end, everyone but Sabito passed that final selection.
As for me, I was left wounded by the very first demon that attacked me. I was helpless.
Me.
At that moment, it was Sabito who saved me.
Water breathing. Fourth form. Striking tide!
After saving me, I was left in the care of another boy.
Then he quickly ran off towards another cry for help.
When I came to, the final selection was over.
While it's true I survived for seven days, therefore passing the selection, I didn't kill a single demon, and had only been saved by another.
And so, can you really say that I passed?
Someone like me isn't worthy of being the water Hashira.
I don't even deserve to stand next to the likes of the other Hashira.
I'm not like them.
Normally, there'd be no place for me in the Demon Slayer core.
Have the real Hashira train you. It's for the best, really.
I'll never manifest a mark.
As for Sabito, there's no doubt he would have.
Just forget about me. You're wasting your time.
I get it. I really do.
I'm sure he thinks he should have been the one to die that day.
I know how that feels, when someone you value more than your own life, ends up dying before you instead.
And worse, dies because they were protecting you.
It's an unending pain.
Sabito, the boy who trained me back on Mount Segiri.
What a strange experience.
Even though they were both already long dead, they taught me how to survive.
I see.
So Sabito went through final selection with Mr. Giyu.
If he survived, he'd be the same age as Mr. Giyu now.
Amazing. Amazing.
He saved everyone during the selection.
Something I couldn't do.
I was barely able to protect myself.
If Sabito were still here, I'm sure that he'd be an incredible swordsman.
That must be part of the reason why Mr. Giyu feels he should have been the one to die.
I get it.
I had that same thought myself.
Mr. Rengoku.
He sacrificed his own life to protect us.
He was incredible.
His kindness rivaled his strength.
And he never faltered.
Right up till the end.
I wished with all my heart that I'd been the one to die instead of Mr. Rengoku that day.
I thought that one day Mr. Rengoku might have been able to kill Muzan.
He already said he believes in you, so you just have to worry about how to get there.
Yes, that's exactly right.
I know that, but I'm not sure what I should say to Mr. Giyu.
No matter how pathetic or embarrassed you may feel, you've got to keep living.
Muzan, though he doesn't acknowledge it.
I can't imagine how hard he must have trained in order to make himself a worthy candidate for Hashira.
The amount of suffering he must have gone through.
It's not my place to criticize Mr. Giyu when I know nothing about him.
But, but there's one thing I have to ask him.
Only then.
Mr. Giyu!
Oh no, he's not stopping.
What Sabito entrusted to you?
Aren't you going to pass it on?
Mr. Giyu!
Don't you dare ever say that you should have died again!
Next time you say that, you and I are through.
It's unforgivable.
Your older sister, who was supposed to be married the next day, knew what was going to happen when she hid you from that demon to protect you.
So how dare you insult her memory by saying something so selfish?
You have to live and carry her memory!
The life your sister gave you with her sacrifice, the future she gave you, you have to pass them on!
Giyu!
It hurts.
The shock and pain I felt when he struck me is coming back to me now so vividly.
Why did I forget until now that conversation with Sabito when it's so important?
I didn't want to remember it because I wouldn't be able to stop the tears.
Remembering made my grief unbearable and left me utterly helpless.
Big sis, Tsutaku. Sabito. I'm sorry.
Oh no. I think I finally broke him.
What do I do? Was that too harsh of me?
Somehow he looks even more depressed than he usually does.
Did I just end up making it worse?
I know. How about a speed eating contest?
If I win the contest, I'll say, let's cheer up and get some training in.
Or something.
Since I haven't been cleared for active duty yet, it's not like I can spar with him or anything.
Mr. Giyu may not talk much, but he wouldn't have to during an eating contest. It's brilliant!
Tanjiro, I know it's a little late, but I'll join the-
Mr. Giyu! I challenge you to an eating contest!
Mr. Giyu! Why?
Listen, about the training program. I didn't hear any mention of Kocho.
So what is it that she's teaching you all?
Ms. Shinobu? I haven't heard anything, actually. I wonder how she is.
Calm down. It's all right.
Big Sis, help me to calm down.
Only the immature are unable to control their emotions.
The immature…
Master, you have returned.
Master, I'll be departing now to receive training from the Lord Wind Hashira.
I see.
Can our training session wait until after the Lord Stone Hashiras?
Unfortunately, I'm not going to be taking part in the Hashira training.
Huh? But… But why?
Kanau? Come over here.
Okay.
So, um… You see…
I want… I want nothing more than to train with you, Master.
Well, now look at you. You've learned to be more candid about giving voice to your feelings.
That's a good sign.
As I thought…
The timing is perfect.
I'd like to tell you…
About the demon who killed my beloved older sister, Kanai.
And also, how to go about killing the same demon.
I believe you're ready.
How did you just tell me that I was jet Marc?
My fate is not?
My mother…
Why John Explore …
And I love you.
Okay.
You've seen us.
isenilation Father, you've seen us.
Me and I am not happy.
Anakin Father, you have seen us before us.
Altyazı M.K.
Thank you.
You really mean that?
Yes, but no racing.
I'd be happy to.
But first, next episode three, fully recovered Tanjiro joins the Hashira training.